Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - 1974-1975
    - Dale R. Corson - Correspondence., 1975 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      Deal, Jack; Said, Hakim Mohammed; Thomas, Michael Tilson; Goodall, William; Hester, James M.; Robert son, William R.
    - Presidential Councillors., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      Ripley, Joseph P.; Noyes, Jansen Sr.
    - Presidential Councillors., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Safety Division Miscellaneous., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 20)
      Muka, Betty O.; Underwood, Dorothea; McDaniel, William E.
    - Safety Division Miscellaneous., 1975 (Box 92, Folder 21)
      Amendments to University Charter.
    - Safety Division Miscellaneous., 1975 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Safety Division - Budget., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Safety Division - Budget., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Contingency Planning., 1969-74 (Box 92, Folder 25)
      Emergency and closing procedures; Photographing students in demonstrations. Contingency Planning Committee.
    - Contingency Planning., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 26)
      Snow emergency plan.
    - Safety Division - Director Search Committee., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 27-30)
      McDaniel, William E.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1969-73 (Box 92, Folder 31)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.; MacColl, Gail S.; Dean, William Tucker; Cook, Alice H. Judicial Administrator Search Committee; Judiciary Committee.
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator. Bugliari, Joseph B.; Sapakie, Alan L.; Kauber, Barbara M., 1973 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator., 1973-74 (Box 92, Folder 33)
      Kauber, Barbara M.
    - Judicial Advisor., 1972-74 (Box 92, Folder 34)
      Kauber, Barbara M.; Provine, Marie.
    - Judicial Advisor., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 35)
      Kauber, Barbara M.; Provine, Marie; Neimeth, Albert C.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1972-73 (Box 92, Folder 36)
      Danelski, David J.; Yaffe, Byron; Hartman, John D.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1973-74 (Box 92, Folder 37)
      Danelski, David J.; Arms, Karen. Committee on the Status of Women; Sex discrimination.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 38)
      Danelski, David J.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Dotson, Arch.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 39)
      Danelski, David J.
    - Vice President and Chief Investment Officer., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 40)
      Horn, Robert T. Office of University Investments.
    - Laboratory of ornithology., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 41)
      Horn, Robert T.; Hooper, Linda.
    - Office of the Provost., 1970-74 (Box 92, Folder 42)
      Knapp, David C.; Tobin, Thomas L.; Plane, Robert A. Division of Biological Sciences.
    - Office of the Provost., 1974 (Box 92, Folder 43)
      Knapp, David C.; Risley, Robert F.; Peterson, Arthur H.; Barlow, Mark. Office of the Vice Provost.
    - Office of the Provost., 1975 (Box 92, Folder 44)
      Knapp, David C. American Jewish Committee.
    - Provost's Committees., 1974-75 (Box 92, Folder 45)
      Knapp, David C. Committee on the Status of Women; Affirmative action.
    - Alexander Baranowski., 1972 (Box 92, Folder 46)
    - Alexander Baranowski., 1967-72 (Box 92, Folder 47)
    - Alexander Baranowski., 1972-75 [1982] (Box 92, Folder 48)
    - Affirmative Action., 1971-72 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Turner, James E.; Greenwald, Eliot J. United States Office for Civil Rights; Committee for Minorities and Disadvantaged Interests.
    - Affirmative Action., 1972 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      Stamp, Neal R. Affirmative Action Program.
    - Affirmative Action., 1972-74 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action., 1972-74 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      Wolf son, Michael I. United States Office for Civil Rights; University of Chicago; Council on Affirmative Action; University of Pittsburgh.
    - Affirmative Action., 1973-74 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      United States Office for Civil Rights.
    - Affirmative Action., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      George-Rodriguez, Nicholas. New York State Division of Human Rights; University of California; Basketball Team.
    - Affirmative Action., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      Wolfson, Michael I.; Gurowitz, William D.; Everett, Chestyn; Black, Pauline L.; Kramer, Henry S. United States Office for Civil Rights; Agency for Educational Innovation.
    - Affirmative Action., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Arent, Albert E.; Bok, Derek C. Council on Affirmative Action.
    - Affirmative Action., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Hodgson, Keith; Kramer, Henry S.; Danelski, David J.; Epstein, Ben j amin R.; Arent, Albert E.; Aschaffenburg, E. Lysle.
    - Affirmative Action., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      Kurlander, Robert; Arms, Karen; Osby, William; Rivera, Ramon E.
    - Affirmative Action., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      Williams, Chester; Breitfeld, Viviane E. T.; Cramton, Roger C. Female faculty statistics.
    - Affirmative Action., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Barlow, Mark; Hardigan, Eileen 0.; Knapp, David C. Equal pay; University of California.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      O'Brien, Richard D.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Morrison, Alan W.; Knapp, David C.; Eisner, Thomas.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Morrison, Alan W.; Gibson, Quentin. "Wing on Wing on Wing11 (Hall).
    - Center for Urban Development Research., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      Knapp, David C.; Tresch, Phillip S.; Van Houweling, Douglas E.; Becker, Franklin D.; Fisher, Gordon P. Regional Science Program.
    - Center for Urban Development Research., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 18)
      Knapp, David C.; Fisher, Gordon P.; Schuler, Richard E.; Parsons, Kermit C. Regional Science Program.
    - Coordinator of State Relations., 1973-75 (Box 93, Folder 19)
      Tobin, Thomas L.; Ruggieri, Bernard; Finnerty, Michael; Dear ing, Bruce; Risley, Robert F.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 20)
      Martin, Louis E.; McCarthy, Stephen A.; Miller, J. Gormly; McGowan, John; Cooke, W. Donald; Knapp, David C.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 21)
      Miller, J. Gormly; Shepherd, Giles F. Board.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 22)
      Miller, J. Gormly; Elledge, Scott B.; Edelman, Hendrik; Knapp, David C.; Kulp, Arthur C.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 23)
      Miller, J. Gormly; Dean, Arthur H.; Brown, J. Carter; Williams, Gordon; Brown, Stuart M. Houdon life mask of Lafayette.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 24)
      Miller, J. Gormly; Brown, Stuart M.; Salton, Gerard. Library computing.
    - Herbert F. Johnson of Art., 1972-75 (Box 93, Folder 25)
      Leavitt, Thomas W.; Olin, Spencer T.; Johnson, Herbert F. American Institute of Architects.
    - Lafayette Collection., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 26)
      Dean, Arthur H.; Besterman, Theodore.
    - New Program Allocations., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 27)
      Leurgans, Paul J.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Gurowitz, William D. "$2.7 Million Fund" (Anonymous Fund # 31); PLATO-IV Computer Assisted Instruction Project.
    - New Program Allocations., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 28)
      Plane, Robert A.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Seznec, Alain. Educational innovation; Latin American Studies Program; Visiting Art Critic Program.
    - New Program Allocations., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 29)
      Parsons, Kermit C. College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.
    - New Program Allocations., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 30)
      Parsons, Kermit C.; Liu, Ta-Chung. Department of Architecture; College of Architecture, Art, and Planning.
    - New Program Allocations., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 31)
      Knapp, David C.; Esman, Milton J.
    - New Program Allocations., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 32)
      New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
    - New Program Allocations., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 33)
      Davidson, H. Just in. Anonymous Fund # 31.
    - New Program Allocations., 1972-73 (Box 93, Folder 34)
      PLATO-IV Computer Assisted Instruction Project; College of Engineering.
    - New Program Allocations., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 35)
      Rudan, John W. Interactive Computing Facility; Women's Studies Program; Program on Science, Technology and Society.
    - Mew Program Allocations., 1973 (Box 93, Folder 36)
      Kahn, Alfred E. College of Engineering; Educational innovation.
    - New Program Allocations., 1973-74 (Box 93, Folder 37)
      McGinnis, Robert. Program for Social Analyses of Science Systems; Andrew W. Mellon Foundation.
    - New Program Allocations., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 38)
      Liu, Ta-Chung; Cooke, W. Donald. Anonymous Fund # 31; Computer-Oriented Social Sciences Information Service; Committee on Social Science Computing.
    - Andrew Dickson White Professors-at-large. Black, Max; Noyes, Nicholas H.; Morris, Norval., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Society for the Humanities., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 40)
      Black, Max; Guerlac, Henry; Levin, Harry; Barlow, Mark; Thorp, Charles M.; Young, Martie W.; Risley, Robert F.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Seznec, Alain. Andrew Dickson White House.
    - Society for the Humanities., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 41)
      Guerlac, Henry; Knapp, David C.; Ramin, Richard M.; Levin, Harry; Blackall, Eric A.; Pusey, Nathan M.; Kahn, Alfred E. Andrew W. Mellon Foundation.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Budget and Funds., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 42)
      Turner, James E.; Knapp, David C. ASRC Library.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center -Budget and Funds., 1974-75 (Box 93, Folder 43)
      Turner, James E.; Knapp, David C.; Casarett, Alison P. Institute of Afro-American Affairs at New York University; ASRC Library.
    - James E. Turner Tenure Review., 1975 (Box 93, Folder 44)
    - CO8EP Advisory Committee., 1973-75 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      Cranch, E. T.; Knapp, David C.; McKersie, Robert B.
    - CO8EP. Carr, Carson; Reed, Clarence., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - COSEP., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      Richardson, Henry W.
    - COSEP., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      Hunter, Delridge. COSEP accounts.
    - COSEP., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      Hunter, Delridge; Barlow, Mark. COSEP attrition and grades.
    - COSEP., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      Hunter, Delridge; Garrett, James B.; Dickason, Donald G.
    - COSEP - Learning Skills Center., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      Mosley, Mary S.
    - COSEP - Learning Skills Center. Mosley, Mary S.; Knapp, David C., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Black Miscellaneous., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      Jones, William D.; Williams, Ronald L. African Students Association; Cornell University Medical College; Ujamaa Residential College.
    - Minority Education., 1973-74 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      George-Rodriguez, Nicholas; Kahn, Alfred E.; Hunter, Delridge. Cornell Latin American and Puerto Rican students; Ethnic Studies Program; New Coalition.
    - Minority Education., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      Santiago, Eliasib; Boricua, Taller. COSEP; Puerto Rican Workshop.
    - Minority Education., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      Everhart, W. Harry; Dickason, Donald G.; Sola, Donald F. Committee on Minorities and Disadvantaged Interests; Asian-American students; COSEP.
    - Native American Association., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      Jamieson, Janine.
    - Office of the Vice Provost., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      Manor, James G.; Shannon, David A.; Shannon, Edgar F.
    - Office of the Vice Provost., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      Barlow, Mark; Knapp, David C.; Pauk, Walter. Memorial University of Newfoundland.
    - Office of the Vice Provost., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      Barlow, Mark; Walker, Jay; Drinkwater, David; Weiss, Stephen H.
    - Office of the vice Provost., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      Barlow, Mark; Taylor, Vail M.
    - Office of Admissions., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Office of Admissions., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 19)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Barlow, Mark; Storandt, Robert W. Application fees.
    - Office of Admissions., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 20)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Barlow, Mark; Storandt, Robert W.; Slater, John E. Early Decision Program.
    - Office of Admissions., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 21)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Storandt, Robert W.; Gerstein, Dorothy.
    - Office of Admissions., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 22)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Barlow, Mark; Storandt, Robert W.
    - Office of Admissions., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 23)
      Barlow, Mark; Stone, Margaret; Scott, Robert A.
    - Office of Admissions., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 24)
      Barlow, Mark; Snickenberger, Walter A.; McCalmon, Byron G.; Bellamy, William M.; Failing, Jean; Dickason, Donald G.
    - Office of Admissions., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 25)
      Barlow, Mark. Admissions reorganization.
    - Admissions Study., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 26)
      Barlow, Mark. Committee on Admissions.
    - Admissions Study., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid -Search and Reorganization., 1973-75 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid -Search and Reorganization., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 29)
      Barlow, Mark; Storandt, Robert W.; Averill, Janet S.; De Winter, Urbain J.; Bisselle, Philip M.; Dickason, Donald G.
    - Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid -Search and Reorganization., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 30)
      Barlow, Mark; Morse, Barbara; Norton, Mary Beth; Stewart, Charles T.
    - Center for the Improvement of Undergraduate Education., 1972-74 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Center for the Improvement of Undergraduate Education., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 32)
      Maas, James B.; Barlow, Mark; Parsons, Kermit C. Committee on Academic Programs and Policies.
    - Center for the Improvement of Undergraduate Education., 1975 (Box 94, Folder 33)
      Maas, James B.; Barlow, Mark; Knapp, David C.; Gluck, David.
    - Continuing Education., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Division of Unclassified students., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970-71 (Box 94, Folder 36)
      Whyte, William Foote; Reed, Theodore L.; Eagle, Vernon A.; Nichols, Benjamin; Carter, Lisle C. New World Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 94, Folder 37)
      Whyte, William Foote; Neisser, Ulric; Smith, John Lee.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 94, Folder 38)
      Whyte, William Foote. Educational Policy Board.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 94, Folder 39)
      Whyte, William Foote; Jackson, R. Peter; Natelson, Robert G.; Reed, Theodore L.; Goldman, Jack. Cornell Campus Coalition.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1973-74 (Box 94, Folder 40)
      Barlow, Mark; Stamp, Neal R.; Bereano, Nancy K.; Knapp, David C.; Whyte, William Foote.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1973-74 (Box 94, Folder 41)
      Barlow, Mark; Leahy, Daniel B.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 42)
      Leahy, Daniel B.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 43)
      Whyte, William Foote.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 44)
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 45)
    - Human Affairs Program., 1972-73 (Box 94, Folder 46)
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 47)
      Dowd, Virginia M.; Hildebrand, George H.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 48)
      Leahy, Daniel B.; Catherwood, Martin P.
    - Human Affairs Program. Catherwood, Martin P.; Myers, William I.; Barlow, Mark; Lyons, William A.; Levin, Harry; Leahy, Daniel B. Committee on Independent Courses., 1974 (Box 94, Folder 49)
    - Human Affairs Program., 1974-75 (Box 94, Folder 50)
      Barlow, Mark; Myers, William I.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1975-76 (Box 94, Folder 51)
      Dowd, Virginia M.; Barlow, Mark; Lyons, William A.; Myers, William I. People's Power Coalition of New York.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      Moch, Michael; Carter, Lisle C.; Whyte, William Foote; Turner, James E. Ford Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      Bard, Bruce H.; Carter, Lisle C.; Abbott, Edward P.; Nichols, Benjamin; Whyte, William Foote.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Salt ford, Richard A.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1970-71 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      Carter, Lisle C.; Whyte, William Foote; Esolen, Gary. Russell Sage Foundation; Ford Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Risley, Robert F.; Whyte, William Foote; Carter, Lisle C. New World Foundation.
    - Human Affairs Program., 1971 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      Nichols, Benjamin; Kennedy, W. Keith; Stutz, Frederick H.; Carter, Lisle C.; Higgins, Doria.
    - Pre-medical Advisory Committee., 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      Barlow, Mark; Suchman, Anthony L. Students' Project on Cornell Health Education.
    - Pre-medical Advisory Committee., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      Barlow, Mark; Gasteiger, Edgar L.
    - ROTC., 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - ROTC., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      Barlow, Mark; McPeek, William C.; Risley, Robert F.
    - ROTC., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      Barlow, Mark; Doak, Samuel L.; McPeek, William C.
    - ROTC., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      McPeek, William C.; Barlow, Mark.
    - ROTC., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      McPeek, William C.; Orear, Jay; Luisi, Gerard H. Eisenhower College; Ithaca College.
    - ROTC., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      Barlow, Mark; McPeek, William C. Tompkins Cortland Community College.
    - ROTC., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      Barlow, Mark; Brickel, James R.
    - State Regional Meetings., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      Lance, Richard H.; Hall, Jackson O. Council of Higher Education Institution Presidents.
    - Program on Science, Technology and Society., 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      Black, Max; Brown, Stuart M.; Bowers, Raymond. Johnson Foundation.
    - Program on Science, Technology and Society., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      Bowers, Raymond.
    - Program on Science, Technology and Society., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      Bowers, Raymond; Nelkin, Dorothy; Brown, Stuart M.; Barlow, Mark.
    - Program on Science, Technology and Society., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      Bowers, Raymond; Milch, Jerome E. Biology and Science Curriculum Committee.
    - Program on Science, Technology and Society. Bowers, Raymond; Black, Max., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Research Program for the Social Analyses of Science systems (SASS)., 1972-73 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      McGinnis, Robert; White, D. Hywel. National Science Foundation.
    - Research Program for the Social Analyses of Science systems (SASS)., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      McGinnis, Robert; Cooke, W. Donald.
    - Research Program for the Social Analyses of Science systems (SASS)., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      McGinnis, Robert; Cooke, W. Donald; Barlow, Mark; Calkins, Ann.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Barlow, Mark; Wells, Guy E. Risley College.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Barlow, Mark; Jermy, Charles W.; Gurowitz, Sandra P.; Brock, Stephen C. Ithaca College.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 27)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Barlow, Mark; Danelski, David J. Course auditing.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 28)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Barlow, Mark.
    - Division of Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 29)
      Sampson, Martin W.; Barlow, Mark; Gortzig, Jean. American Association of University Women; Course auditing.
    - Teacher Preparation., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 30)
      Levin, Harry; Unsworth, Peg; Rhodes, Kathleen.
    - Tuition., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 31)
      Cranch, E. T.; Lambert, William W.; Parsons, Kermit C.
    - Tuition., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 32)
      Snickenberger, Walter A.; Lawrence, Samuel A.
    - Tuition., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - Office of the Vice Provost - McKeegan., 1972-73 (Box 95, Folder 34)
      McKeegan, Paul L. University music programs.
    - Office of the Vice Provost - McKeegan., 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 35)
      McKeegan, Paul L.; Plane, Robert A.
    - Cornell University Press., 1973-75 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      Howley, Roger.
    - Vice President for Research., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Cayuga Station Project., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 38)
      Carigg, J. A.; Rogers, Thomas R. New York State Electric and Gas Corporation.
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo ionospheric Observatory., 1972 (Box 95, Folder 39)
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research * Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 40)
      Doundoulakis, Helias; Callagher, Barrett.
    - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 41)
      Adel, Arthur; Sagan, Carl; Salpeter, E. E.; Gold, Thomas; Drake, Frank D.
    - Arecibo Ionospheric observatory Advisory Board., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 42)
      Drake, Frank D.
    - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory Advisory Board., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 43)
      Drake, Frank D.; Jones, Thomas O.
    - Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory Advisory Board., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 44)
      Drake, Frank D.; Van Alien, James.
    - Center for Environmental Quality Management., 1974 (Box 95, Folder 45)
      Lynn, Walter R.; Cooke, W. Donald; Rogers, Thomas R. Anonymous Fund # 31; Cayuga Station; New York State Electric and Gas Corporation.
    - Center for Environmental Quality Management., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 46)
      Lynn, Walter R.; Cooke, W. Donald; Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Center for International Studies., 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 47)
      Esman, Milton J.; Kammen, Michael G.; Golay, Frank H.; Kennedy, W. Keith. Ford Foundation; Canadian Studies.
    - Center for International Studies., 1975 (Box 95, Folder 48)
      Esman, Milton J.; Sharp, Lauriston; Killeen, Sean. Ford Foundation; Southeast Asia Program.
    - Cornell Research Foundation., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 49)
      Tyler, Winfield W.; Stamp, Neal R.; Rogers, Thomas R.
    - Laboratory of Nuclear studies., 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 50)
      DeWire, John W.; Silverman, Albert; McDaniel, Boyce D.; Phillips, Lawrence.
    - Laboratory of Atomic and Solid State Physics (LASSP)., 1973-75 (Box 95, Folder 51)
      Truschke, Edward F.; Rogers, John B.; Chester, Geoffrey V.; Kahn, Alfred E. Xerox Corporation.
    - Patent Administration., 1972-74 (Box 95, Folder 52)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Rogers, Thomas R.; Stamp, Neal R.; Barnard, Ralph R.; Lawrence, Samuel A. Cornell Research Foundation; University patent policy.
    - Patent Administration., 1974-75 (Box 95, Folder 53)
      Cooke, W. Donald; Rogers, Thomas R.; Stamp, Neal R.; Ramin, Richard M.; Long, Franklin A. Patent and Invention Policy for Cornell University; Cornell Research Foundation.
    - Vice President for Administration., 1974 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Lawrence, Samuel A. Academic taxonomy.
    - Vice President for Administration. Lawrence, Samuel A. Responsibility Center Analysis Funds for Subvention and Reconciliation to Financial Statements., 1974 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Vice President for Administration., 1974-75 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Barton, David W.; Ostrom, John S. Responsibility Center.
    - Budget 1974-75., 1973-75 (Box 96, Folder 4-13)
    - Budget Discussion Papers., 1974-75 (Box 96, Folder 14-17)
    - Department of Buildings and Properties., 1974 (Box 96, Folder 18)